swik.net 2009-02-15

# Privacy Policy - SWiK

At SourceLabs, Inc., we respect your right to privacy and we understand that visitors to our home page [http://www.sourcelabs.com](http://www.sourcelabs.com/) or to our Swik web site at [http://swik.net](http://swik.net/) need to control the uses of their personal information. Our SourceLabs site allows individuals to learn about our company and product and services offerings. Our Swik site provides a wide range of interactive services and offerings. The privacy policy below describes the measures taken by us to protect your privacy in connection with your use of our web sites. 

What personally identifiable information do we collect, and how do we use it?

  * **Registration**. You may elect to establish an account with us. If you do, we will collect certain registration data from you, including your name, e-mail address, handle, and other information on the registration form. We use this registration information to operate our services, track projects, monitor user activity, maintain discussion forums, and otherwise to improve our web sites. Also we may display some of your personal information (e.g. your name or handle) to other users, such as when you are the leader of a project, or when you post messages on discussion boards. We will not display or share your e-mail address with others unless you expressly permit us to do so (opt-in).
  * **IP Address**. An internet protocol (IP) address is a unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your internet service provider. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We collect and use your IP address to operate our services, track your usage of the site, to manage forum posts and content and database modifications, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our sites. We may also display your IP address to users of our sites when you use our services. Your IP address also may be used to gather broad demographic information.
  * **Cookies**. A cookie is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain web sites. We use cookies to track how frequently users come to our sites, to determine where our users are coming from, to determine what type of systems our users use, and to help the services operate. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your personally identifiable information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit other web sites you may be required to accept cookies. Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.
  * **E-mail**. If you register with our site and you elect to receive e-mails and news from us (opt-in), we may send you e-mail messages with SourceLabs or Swik news and information. Even if you do not elect to receive (or opt-out of receiving) news from us, we may use your e-mail address from time to time to contact you about your account.
  * **Special Contests or Promotions**. We may occasionally present a special contest or promotion, which may or may not be sponsored by another company. To qualify for entry in such contest or promotion, we may ask you to provide personal information. If we plan to share your personal information with a sponsor(s) or with others, we will provide a statement to that effect in the contest or promotion terms.

Who do we share your personally identifiable information with?

  * We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties, aside from entities that perform services for us that either are bound to comply with our privacy policy or have privacy policies that protect your information. 

However, we may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone's safety. 

  * As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets, and, depending upon the transaction, your personally identifiable information may be one of the transferred assets. In the event that we are acquired by another company, your personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party.

What are your options to control the use of your personally identifiable information? 

  * If, after you opt-in at the time of registration to receive e-mails and news from us, you would rather not receive such communications, please click on the 'unsubscribe' link at the bottom of the e-mail you receive, or send an email to [unsubscribe@sourcelabs.com](mailto:unsubscribe@sourcelabs.com) and follow the instructions to unsubscribe. You may also contact us by postal mail at 411 1st Avenue South, Suite 750, Seattle, Washington 98104, Attention: Opt-out. 

How can I update my profile?

  * Please maintain the accuracy profiles by notifying us when you change your address, title, phone number or e-mail address. If at any time you wish to update your information or stop receiving communication from us, you may visit the registration page. 

What about kids. personally identifiable information?

  * Our sites are not directed to children under the age of 13. We respect the privacy of parents and children and are committed to complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ('COPPA'). 
  * If a parent believes that his or her child has provided us with personal information, he or she can contact us via e-mail or postal mail as listed below. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13. 
  * We believe that parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from otherwise disclosing online their name, address and other personal information without parental permission. 

What else should you know about your privacy? 

  * **Security**. We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. These security measures include a firewall to prevent unauthorized access to our systems. Although we will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure.
  * **Links to Other Sites**. Our sites contain hyperlinks and pointers to Internet sites maintained by third parties. These links are provided for your reference only. We do not control, operate or endorse in any respect information, products or services on such third-party sites and are not responsible for their content. Many third-party sites have their own privacy policies that differ from ours. This privacy policy only covers our sites and does not cover any other site. While we make every effort to keep your information secure, we do not control the policies of other sites.

Changes to this privacy policy

  * We may make changes in our privacy policy from time to time. When we do so, we will post the revised privacy policy on our sites with a link at the bottom of our home page. Our home page will also contain a statement notifying readers that the policy has changed and the effective date of that change.

Contacting SourceLabs

  * We would like to receive your comments and questions about this Privacy Policy and any other matter you have regarding our sites. Please address comments or questions to us via e-mail or postal mail.  
You can send e-mails to:  
You may also contact us by mail:   
SourceLabs, Inc.  
411 First Avenue South  
Suite 750  
Seattle, Washington 98104 

Acceptance of privacy policy 

Your use of our sites is subject to this Privacy Policy. BY USING OUR SITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the bottom of this page to determine if the policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of our sites following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.
